人生这么短
Life is so short
还这么美好
And oh so sweet
阳光中的生命
Life in the sun
是这么优雅
Is such a treat
随心所欲
Do what you want to do
停下来看看风景
Pause take in the view
别让它轻易流逝
Don't let it pass you by
没道理感到忧郁
No point in feeling blue
实在是来日苦短
Our days are only few,
快实现你的梦想
Make your dreams come alive
大笑之
Smile big
且和世界分享
And share it with the world
照耀着
Shine bright
散发你的光芒
Spread your light
你得好好享受这儿的一切
It's all here for you to enjoy
每天都是你生命中的第一天
Every day is the first day of your life
生命就如同
Life is a breeze
你放松时刮来的微风
When you're at ease
生命是那个需要你满足他的人
Life is what you make it please
随心所欲
Be what you want to be
体会自由与狂野
Feeling wild and free
别让他人拖住你
Don't let 'em drag you down
如你所见
As far as you can see
爬最高的树
Climb up the highest tree
快实现你的梦想
Make your dreams come alive
大笑之
Smile big
且和世界分享
And share it with the world
照耀着
Shine bright
散发你的光芒
Spread your light
你得好好享受这儿的一切
It's all here for you to enjoy
每天都是你生命中的第一天
Every day is the first day of your life
每天也是你余下生命中的最美好的一天
Every day is the best day of the rest of your life